♪Fade like drifting clouds♪
♪تتلاشى مثل السحب المنجرفة♪
♪Half dream, half illusion♪
♪نصف حلم، ونصف وهم♪
♪Fated or fleeting♪
♪مقدر أو عابر♪
♪Spring breeze falls from my brow♪
♪نسائم الربيع تهب من جبهتي♪
♪Where to go, I do not know♪
♪أين أذهب، لا أعرف♪
♪I turn, and all is gone♪
♪أتحول، وكل شيء قد ذهب♪
♪Ask how deep the dust of love runs♪
♪اسأل عن مدى عمق غبار الحب♪
♪How strong longing grows♪
♪ما أشد الشوق الذي ينمو♪
♪I play till the final note♪
♪ألعب حتى النغمة الأخيرة♪
=In The Name of Loyalty=
=باسم الولاء=
=Episode 18=
=الحلقة 18=
Yet you've acted this way.
ولكنك تصرفت بهذه الطريقة.
How dare you shame our family?
كيف تجرؤ على إحراج عائلتنا؟
Zhiying,
تشي ينغ،
tell me.
أخبرني.
Who's the father of the child?
من هو والد الطفل؟
Only by telling me
فقط عن طريق إخباري
can I stand up for you.
هل يمكنني الوقوف بجانبك؟
I don't know either.
انا أيضا لا اعرف.
Wait.
انتظر.
How could you not know? You...
كيف لا تعرف؟ أنت...
Your Majesty.
جلالتك.
Your Majesty! Your Majesty!
جلالتك! جلالتك!
Bad news!
اخبار سيئة!
The Prince Regent's forces have surrounded the palace.
لقد حاصرت قوات الأمير الوصي القصر.
Let me ask you.
دعني أسألك.
Where did His Majesty
أين جلالته؟
and Cheng Ge go two nights ago?
وذهب تشنغ جي منذ ليلتين؟
I don't know.
لا أعرف.
I'll ask once more.
سأسأل مرة أخرى.
Where exactly did His Majesty
أين بالضبط جلالته؟
and Cheng Ge go two nights ago?
وذهب تشنغ جي منذ ليلتين؟
- I truly don't know.
- أنا حقا لا أعرف.
Last chance for you.
فرصتك الاخيرة .
They...
هم...
They went to Imperial Weaving House in the west of city.
ذهبوا إلى Imperial Weaving House في غرب المدينة.
Imperial Weaving House?
بيت النسيج الإمبراطوري؟
I got it.
حصلت عليه.
Gao Ji!
جاو جي!
You...
أنت...
Why did you kill them?
لماذا قتلتهم؟
Protect His Majesty.
حماية جلالته.
He can't leave the palace.
لا يستطيع مغادرة القصر.
- Yes!
- نعم!
(Imperial Weaving House)
(دار النسيج الإمبراطورية)
(Accumulated Momentum)
(الزخم المتراكم)
How dare you!
كيف تجرؤ!
You dare blockade His Majesty's chamber?
هل تجرؤ على حصار غرفة جلالته؟
Is the Prince Regent
هل الأمير الوصي؟
attempting to kill His Majesty?
محاولة قتل جلالته؟
General,
عام،
by the Prince Regent's orders,
بأوامر الأمير الوصي،
we're here to protect His Majesty.
نحن هنا لحماية جلالته.
I must report disaster relief matters to His Majesty now.
يجب أن أبلغ جلالته بمسائل الإغاثة من الكوارث الآن.
Move!
يتحرك!
General Yan,
الجنرال يان
the Prince Regent ordered no one enters or leaves.
أمر الأمير الوصي بعدم دخول أو خروج أحد.
This sword was bestowed by His Majesty.
لقد تم منح هذا السيف من قبل جلالته.
If national affairs are delayed,
إذا تأخرت الشؤون الوطنية،
how many lives do you have to lose?
كم عدد الأرواح التي يجب أن تخسرها؟
Move!
يتحرك!
Your Majesty,
جلالتك،
I arrived late to your aid.
لقد وصلت متأخرا لمساعدتك.
Rise, General Yan.
انهض يا جنرال يان.
I saw the Prince Regent's guards approaching
رأيت حراس الأمير الوصي يقتربون
and sensed trouble.
وأحس بالمتاعب.
What's happened?
ماذا حدث؟
How should I resolve this crisis?
كيف يمكنني حل هذه الأزمة؟
There is one thing
هناك شيء واحد
requiring your assistance.
بحاجة إلى مساعدتك.
(Imperial Weaving House)
(دار النسيج الإمبراطورية)
Nan.
في.
Nan!
في!
Shi Nan is quick-witted and cautious.
شي نان هو شخص سريع البديهة وحذر.
Maybe
ربما
he's already escaped.
لقد هرب بالفعل.
Was this medicine prepared as I instructed?
هل تم تحضير هذا الدواء حسب تعليماتي؟
Yes.
نعم.
Your Grace,
صاحب السمو،
the child you are carrying
الطفل الذي تحملينه
is a royal heir.
هو الوريث الملكي.
This abortion potion
هذه جرعة الإجهاض
must not be consumed.
لا يجوز استهلاكه.
I have
أملك
the final say.
الكلمة النهائية.
Ji? What are you doing?
جي؟ ماذا تفعل؟
Your Grace.
صاحب السمو.
Your Grace, are you alright?
صاحب السمو هل أنت بخير؟
Everyone, leave!
الجميع، إرحلوا!
Yes.
نعم.
Do you know why
هل تعلم لماذا
I dare not return power to Shi Yu?
لا أجرؤ على إرجاع السلطة إلى شي يو؟
Because I forced him to kill his own brother
لأني أجبرته على قتل أخيه
and the people of Pingxiang who raised him.
وشعب بينغشيانغ الذي رباه.
Tell me.
أخبرني.
If I restored power to Shi Yu,
إذا قمت باستعادة الطاقة إلى شي يو،
would he spare us?
هل سيوفر علينا؟
I don't fear his revenge,
أنا لا أخاف من انتقامه،
but what about you?
ولكن ماذا عنك؟
What should you do?
ماذا يجب عليك أن تفعل؟
So you mean
فهل تقصد
everything you've done
كل ما فعلته
was for me?
كان لي؟
Zhiying,
تشي ينغ،
I can't protect you forever.
لا أستطيع حمايتك إلى الأبد.
The only way to ensure your safety
الطريقة الوحيدة لضمان سلامتك
is through the royal heir you are carrying.
من خلال الوريث الملكي الذي تحمله.
You don't understand now,
أنت لا تفهم الآن،
but you will in time.
ولكنك ستفعل ذلك مع الوقت.
Everything I'm doing
كل ما أفعله
is for your own good.
هو من أجل مصلحتك.
But this child isn't Shi Yu's.
ولكن هذا الطفل ليس طفل شي يو.
It is his child,
إنه طفله
if I say so.
إذا قلت ذلك.
Ensure the safety of the Empress and the royal heir.
ضمان سلامة الإمبراطورة والوريث الملكي.
If anything happens to them,
إذا حدث لهم أي شيء،
I will hold you all accountable.
سأحملكم جميعا المسؤولية.
Send the order.
أرسل الطلب.
The feast will proceed as planned.
سيتم الاحتفال كما هو مخطط له.
Open our borders wide
افتح حدودنا على مصراعيها
to welcome foreign envoys.
للترحيب بالمبعوثين الأجانب.
Ji.
من.
Your Majesty.
جلالتك.
General Yan, thank you for today.
السيد الجنرال يان، شكرا لك على هذا اليوم.
Your Majesty,
جلالتك،
as you commanded,
كما أمرت
our scouts report
تقرير الكشافة لدينا
Gao Ji took five or six carts of corpses back to the dungeon.
أخذ جاو جي خمس أو ست عربات مليئة بالجثث إلى الزنزانة.
His intentions are unclear.
نواياه غير واضحة.
General Yan,
الجنرال يان
did you see among the corpses
هل رأيت بين الجثث
a man with a badly scarred face?
رجل ذو وجه مليء بالندوب؟
We examined them carefully.
لقد فحصناهم بعناية.
No scarred man was found.
لم يتم العثور على رجل مصاب بندبة.
I think I know where he might be going.
أعتقد أنني أعرف إلى أين قد يكون ذاهبًا.
General Yan,
الجنرال يان
keep this safe for me.
احتفظ بهذا آمنًا بالنسبة لي.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
(Cheng Ge,)
(تشنغ قه،)
(Shi Yu!)
(شي يو!)
(You double-faced traitors)
(أيها الخونة ذوو الوجهين)
(destroyed my weaving house.)
(دمر بيت النسيج الخاص بي.)
(You will pay a hundredfold)
(سوف تدفع مائة ضعف)
(for what I endured today!)
(على ما تحملته اليوم!)
♪Without fate, this dream would fade♪
♪بدون القدر، هذا الحلم سوف يتلاشى♪
♪Without you, my life would quietly end♪
♪بدونك، حياتي ستنتهي بهدوء♪
♪Fade like drifting clouds♪
♪تتلاشى مثل السحب المنجرفة♪
♪Half dream, half illusion♪
♪نصف حلم، ونصف وهم♪
♪Fated or fleeting♪
♪مقدر أو عابر♪
♪Spring breeze falls from my brow♪
♪نسائم الربيع تهب من جبهتي♪
♪Where to go, I do not know♪
♪أين أذهب، لا أعرف♪
♪I turn, and all is gone♪
♪أتحول، وكل شيء قد ذهب♪
♪Ask how deep the dust of love runs♪
♪اسأل عن مدى عمق غبار الحب♪
♪How strong longing grows♪
♪ما أشد الشوق الذي ينمو♪
♪I play till the final note♪
♪ألعب حتى النغمة الأخيرة♪
♪Let fate cut like a blade♪
♪دع القدر يقطع مثل الشفرة♪
♪I bid you one last farewell♪
♪أقول لك وداعا أخيرا♪
♪I know not love's emptiness nor hatred's pain♪
♪لا أعرف فراغ الحب ولا ألم الكراهية♪
♪When we meet again, the snow will melt away♪
♪عندما نلتقي مرة أخرى، سوف يذوب الثلج♪
♪One vow, so deep in love♪
♪عهد واحد، عميق في الحب♪
♪I'd give my life for it♪
♪سأعطي حياتي من أجله♪